[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the medical term for a nosebleed?", "correct_answer": "Rhinorrhagia", "incorrect_answers": ["Rhinitis", "Rhinomycosis", "Rhinodynia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was originally cast as Marty McFly in Back to the Future?", "correct_answer": "Eric Stoltz", "incorrect_answers": ["John Cusak", "Neil Patrick Harris", "Michael J. Fox"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Niacin is the name of this B vitamin.", "correct_answer": "Vitamin B3", "incorrect_answers": ["Vitamin B12", "Vitamin B5", "Vitamin B9"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the birth name of Academy Award-winning actress Jane Fonda?", "correct_answer": "Lady Jayne Seymour Fonda", "incorrect_answers": ["Mary Jayne Seymour Fonda", "Lady Mary Jane Fonda", "Baby Jane Fonda"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This haunting song by Echo  the Bunnymen was used in the opening sequence in the cult classic, Donnie Darko.", "correct_answer": "The Killing Moon", "incorrect_answers": ["Moon Over Bourbon Street", "Season Of The Witch", "Every Day Is Halloween"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the number of amino acids commonly associated with the mammalian protein?", "correct_answer": "20", "incorrect_answers": ["25", "23", "46"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1940 animated film Fantasia featured music by Johann Sebastian Bach.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which genus of plants does catnip (catmint) belong to?", "correct_answer": "Nepeta", "incorrect_answers": ["Nigella", "Nepenthes", "Nyssa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which country has twice rejected European Union membership in national referendums?", "correct_answer": "Norway", "incorrect_answers": ["Poland", "Turkey", "UK"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Claustrophobia means fear of cellars.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What genre is Bernardo Betoluccis movie \u201cThe Conformist\u201d?", "correct_answer": "Political drama", "incorrect_answers": ["Thriller", "Comedy", "Fantasy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where do the Jedi and the Sith store their secrets?", "correct_answer": "holocron", "incorrect_answers": ["Yodas mind", "database", "computer"]}]